{
    "id": "18758a80f7854f149df8e6f68e10b017",
    "title": "Gap Fills",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I want to know why …………………. late.",
            "description": "In indirect questions, the subject goes before the auxiliary verb.",
            "answers": [
                "are you",
                "you are"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "If you had asked me I …………………… you.",
            "description": "In the third conditional, we use a past perfect tense in the if-clause and would have + past participle in the main clause.",
            "answers": [
                "would tell",
                "will tell",
                "would have told"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She would have come if you ………………………. her.",
            "description": "In the third conditional, we use a past perfect tense in the if-clause and would have + past participle in the main clause.",
            "answers": [
                "invited",
                "invites",
                "had invited"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The more you praise him, ……………………. he becomes.",
            "description": "In this structure, we need the + comparative in both clauses.",
            "answers": [
                "worse",
                "the worse",
                "the worst"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "No sooner had the teacher entered the class …………………….. the students stood up.",
            "description": "Sooner is a comparative word use than after it. ",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "when",
                "before"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Would you mind …………………….. me your book?",
            "description": "The ing form is used after do you mind and would you mind.",
            "answers": [
                "lending",
                "to lend",
                "lend"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He is too lazy …………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to work",
                "to working",
                "for work"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He enjoys ……………………. with children.",
            "description": "Enjoy cannot be followed by a to-infinitive. ",
            "answers": [
                "playing",
                "to play",
                "to playing"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He accused me …………………… stealing his watch.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "of",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He congratulated me ……………………… my success.",
            "description": "Both for and on can be used.",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "on",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He was acquitted …………………… the charges levelled against him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "of",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………….. the bell rang, the students rushed to the class.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "No sooner",
                "Hardly",
                "As soon as"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}